Guide to the Donald F. Clark Collection circa 1642-1920 MS 118
New-York Historical Society
- Grant, Lt. Robert, 71st Regiment, N.Y. Printed draft to Robert Grant, Esq., London, for 50 pounds. New York, N.Y., 1782 November 7 (Box 1, Item 30)
- Wales, Eleazer. Pay to Charles Treat for his service in the Continental Army for 1780, 1782 November 20 (Box 3, Item 352)
  29 pounds, 12 shillings and 7 pence.
- Wales, Eleazer. Pay to Charles Jones for his service in the Continental Army for 1780, 1782 November 25 (Box 3, Item 356)
  Payment of 10 pounds, 13 shillings and 6 pence.
- Pearle, Frederick. Pay voucher for service in the Continental Army, 1783 January 14 (Box 1, Item 113)
  Printed and signed by William Moseley, Committee.
- Wales, Eleazer. Pay to Robert Watkins for his service in the Continental Army for 1781, 1783 January 15 (Box 3, Item 354)
  Payment of 18 pounds, 17 shillings and 7 pence.
- Wales, Eleazer. Pay to Hezekiah Wheeler for his service in the Continental Army for 1780, 1783 January 20 (Box 3, Item 351)
  Payment of 26 pounds, six shillings and 7 pence.
- Wales, Eleazer. Pay to Hezekiah Wheeler for his service in the Continental Army for 1781, 1783 January 20 (Box 3, Item 353)
  Payment of 18 pounds, 16 shillings and 6 pence.
- Wales, Eleaer. Pay to John Vibbert for his service in the Continental Army for 1780, 1783 January 27 (Box 3, Item 355)
  Payment of 5 pounds, 5 shillings, and 8 pence.
- Clinton, George. Letter to Col. Cortlandt. Kingston, 1783 January 28 (Box 3, Item 307)
  Original returned, photocopy only. Regarding deficiency of regiment.
- Sheafe, Henry. Receipt. Received of Timothy Pickering, 1783 March 7 (Box 1, Item 42)
- Stevens, E. Receipt. West Point, 1783 March 25 (Box 2, Item 241)
- Hathorn, John, NY Speaker of the Assembly. Bill for compensation for attendance, 1783 April (Box 4, Item 510)
- Nicola, Lewis. Receipt. Constitution Island, 1783 April 23 (Box 1, Item 39)
- Walton, William. Magistrate of Police. Pass for Sylvanus Martin. New York City, 1783 April 28 (Box 4, Item 506)
- Swartwout, Jacobus. Deed with Thomas Burroughs. Rumbout Precinct, Dutchess County, 1783 May 1 (Box 4, Item 559)
- Swartwout, Jacobus, Jacob Griffen and John B. Van Wyck. Deed with Martin Schenck. Fishkill, Dutchess County, 1783 May 1 (Box 4, Item 562)
- Butler, Zebulon. Certification of Service. West Point, NY, 1783 May 12 (Box 4, Item 536)
  Stating that Nathaniel Thompson served in Connecticut Regiment.
- Knox, Major General Henry. Note that James Knowles engaged in service for the United States, 1783 June 4 (Box 2, Item 187)
- Pickering, Timothy, QMG. Letter to Major Campbell. Newburgh, 1783 June 6 (Box 1, Item 133)
  Regarding non-commissioned officers' pay.
- Washington, George. Discharge of Nicholas Van Derbogant, 1783 June 8 (Box 1, Item 139)
  Contains Presidential signature.
- Thompson, Sergeant Nathaniel. Payment for Services due. Hartford, 1783 June 11 (Box 4, Item 531)
- Thompson, Sergeant Nathaniel. Payment for Services due. Hartford, 1783 June 11 (Box 4, Item 535)
- Goldsmith, Richard and William Hudson. Deed. Cornwall, Orange County. NY, 1783 June 13 (Box 2, Item 235)
- Goldsmith, Richard. Deed with William Hudson, 1783 June 14 (Box 1, Item 146)
- Barde, John. Letter to Major A. Prevost. Hemstead, Long Island, 1783 June 24 (Box 1, Item 114)
  Letter says to leave to go to York.
- Malcolm, William. Letter to Aaron Burr, Esq. Windsor, 1783 August 25 (Box 1, Item 56)
- Clinton, George. Letter to constituents. Albany, 1783 September 4 (Box 1, Item 106)
  States that the "final establishment of our Independence...answer the expectations of my Constituents in my future Administration."
- Delancey, General Oliver. Receipt for Rations of Forage from Sept. 1 - Oct. 31, 1783, 1783 October 31 (Box 2, Item 195)
- Westerle, E. Letter to Colonel William Duer. Albany, 1783 November 18 (Box 2, Item 263)
- Knox, Henry. Letter to Governor Clinton. West Point, 1783 December 22 (Box 3, Item 315)
  Letter contains a thank you to the troops.
- Knox, Henry. Discharge for Isaac Wilkins, 1783 December 31 (Box 2, Item 250)
- Smith, Melancton. Certificate of Attendance at Temporary Government of the Southern District, 1784 June 24 (Box 2, Item 207)
- Duer, William. Letter to Stephen Lush. New York, 1784 August 9 (Box 2, Item 205)
  Regarding visit from Dr. Thompson.
- Hancock, John's Grocery and Liquor Account kept by William Dodd, 1784 September 25-1785 September 26 (Box 1, Item 110)
- Clinton, Alexander. Resolution of the State of New York, Assembly and Senate, 1784 November 26 (Box 3, Item 388)
  Regarding monument of General Montgomery.
- Sheridan, Henry. Sworn Document Appointing Charles Sade his agent. Parrish of St. Martin in the Fields, 1786 February 1 (Box 2, Item 185)
  Also signed by John Dawson.
- Livingston, Walter and Arthur Lee. Letter to Gerard Bancker, Treasurer of State of New York. Board of Treasury, 1786 May 29 (Box 3, Item 332)
  Letter stating that the US Treasury is quite reduced.
- Hait, John. Receipt of Jonathan Slauson & C. Bates, 1786 April 1 (Box 5, Item 575)
- Hait, John. Receipt of David Slauson, 1786 August 30 (Box 5, Item 574)
- Morris, Robert. Letter. Philadelphia, 1787 June 23 (Box 1, Item 130)
  Regarding a lease.
- Foote, Eli. Letter to Messrs. Ebenezer and Justin Foote of New Marlborough. Guilford, 1787 July 2 (Box 1, Item 15)
- Assembly of New York. Journal of the 11th Session, 1788. Poughkeepsie, 1788 January 9 (Box 5, Item 570)
- Roche, Thomas. Letter to Ebenezer Foote of New Marlborough. New York, N.Y., 1788 April 1 (Box 1, Item 16)
- Morris, Francis Anderson. Letter to Capt. E. Foote of New Marlborough. Newburgh, 1788 April 13 (Box 1, Item 17)
- Clinton, George. Commission to Oliver L. Kerr, 1788 April 26 (Box 3, Item 380)
  Inspector of Brigade of Militia in Orange County.
- Foster, Emerson. Letters to Messrs. Ebenezer and Justin Foote. Orange, 1788 May 30 (Box 1, Item 18)
- Hardy, Joseph. Letter to John Burrall. Office Accounts, Quartermaster's Department, NY, 1788 September 7 (Box 2, Item 251)
- Washington, George. Commendation to Captain George Hurblat, 1788 December 8 (Box 1, Item 140)
  Copy of letter.
- Britt, Theodorus. Letter to John Fisher. Fishkill Landing, 1788 December 23 (Box 2, Item 252)
  Regarding clothing.
- Foote, Justin. Letter to Ebenezer Foote, 1789 April 7 (Box 1, Item 19)
- Huntington, J., Treasurer. Pay for Revolutionary War solider, Captain Elijah Tisdale, 1790 January 9 (Box 4, Item 532)
- Clinton, George, Governor of New York. Patent to Abraham Springsteen (oversize), 1790 August 11 (Box OS-Small, Item 526)
  See Y-Clark Small, Donald F., Collection. Oversize small.
- Burnet, James. Quitclaim. New Windsor, NY, 1790 September 17 (Box 3, Item 377)
- Knox, General Henry. Letter to Gerard Bancker. War Department, 1791 January 8 (Box 1, Item 119)
  Petition of William Reynolds, solider in militia of Orange County, New York.
- Stephens, John. Deed with Daniel Slauson. Stamford, Fairfield County, CT, 1791 February 21 (Box 5, Item 576)
- Maltbie, David. Deed with Daniel Slauson. Stamford, Fairfield County, CT, 1791 February 21 (Box 5, Item 577)
- Havershaw, Precinct and Town. Records kept by Town Clerk of Clarkstown. Town Meeting, 1st Tuesday in April 1791. Rockland County, 1791-1853 (Box 5, Item 598)
  355 pages
- Clinton, George, Governor of New York, and Dewitt Clinton. Resolution to the Council of Revision, 1792 March 13 (Box 4, Item 527)
  Regarding dividing town of Southold in Suffolk County.
- DeWitt, Simeon, NY Surveyor General. Deed with Stephen and Moses DeWitt. Tioga County, 1792 July 17 (Box 3, Item 438)
  Ulysses number 25.
- Davis, John. Will. New Windsor, 1792 September 7 (Box 3, Item 461)
- Waterbury, Ebenezer. Receipt of Jonathan Slauson. Stamford, 1792 December 6 (Box 5, Item 573)
- Clinton, George. Appointment of Chauncey Hyde, 1793 January 7 (Box 1, Item 127)
- Foote, Justin. Letter to Ebenezer Foote, 1793 March 27 (Box 1, Item 20)
- Foote, Justin. Letter to Ebenezer Foote, 1793 April 11 (Box 1, Item 21)
- Cowley, Joseph. Receipt of Messrs. Avery & Tracey. New York, 1793 May 8 (Box 3, Item 435)
- Authorised list of Votes for Assembly, Ulster County, 1793 May 28-29 (Box 1, Item 122)
- Cadwell, Harry. Letter to Ebenezer Foote. New York, N.Y., 1793 September 28 (Box 1, Item 22)
- Clinton, George. Deed to Daniel Byrnes. Ulster County, 1793 October 28 (Box 3, Item 408)
  Regarding tract of land in Newburgh.
- Fansher, Nemiah. Receipt of Jonathan Slauson for Doctoring. North Stamford, 1794 April 19 (Box 5, Item 572)
- Hothom, William. Letter to F.J. Jackson, Esq. Britannia, Ledhorn Road, 1795 February 26 (Box 1, Item 47)
  Regarding Spanish Minister's cooperation of the two squadrons; advises to spare four or five ships.
- Foote, Justin. Letter to Ebenezer Foote. New York, N.Y., 1795 May 2 (Box 1, Item 23)
- Mandevill, Jacob. Deed with Hugh Walsh. Newburgh, NY, 1795 August 5 (Box 4, Item 489)
- Brown, William. Affidavit of account of all goods on ship, Portland James Hussey. City of New York, 1795 October 22 (Box 3, Item 322)
- Doty, Jacob. Affidavit of account of goods on ship, Portland James Hussey. City of New York, 1795 October 23 (Box 3, Item 326)
- Hedges, Phineas. Title page of Strictures on the Elementa Medicine of Dr. Brow, Goshen: David M. Wescott, 1795 (Box 1, Item 1)
- Stamp Office. Certificate for Annual Payment of Hair Powder Tax. Sir Henry Clinton. London, 1795 (Box 3, Item 427)
- Foote, Justin. Letter. Newburgh, 1796 January 18 (Box 1, Item 24)
- Glen, Mrs. Elizabeth. Letter (Dutch) to Henry Glen, Esq. of Philadelphia. Schnectady, 1796 January 27 (Box 2, Item 192)
- Foote, Justin. Letter to Ebenezer Foote. Newburgh, 1796 February 29 (Box 1, Item 25)
- Rochefontaine, Lt. Colonel Stephen. Letter. West Point, N.Y., 1796 March 9 (Box 1, Item 8)
- Brooks, Thomas. Agreement by Brooks et al with Thomas Waters. Cornwall, NY, 1796 March 21 (Box 3, Item 393)
- Tousard, Lewis. Letter to Colonel Ben Walker. New York, NY, 1796 March 24 (Box 1, Item 14)
  Includes in folder is article about Lewis Tousard reprinted from Military Affairs, Volume 24, No. 4, Winter 1960-61.
- North, Thomas and Thomas Waters. Deed. New Cornwall, Orange County, NY, 1796 March 25 (Box 2, Item 244)
- Clinton, George. Indenture between George Clinton and George Washington, 1796 September 6 (Box 1, Item 141)
- Rochefontaine, Stephen, Colonel. Letter to Benjamin Walker. West Point, NY, 1797 May 3 (Box 1, Item 35)
- Clinton, George. Letter to Robert H. Livingston. Greenwich, 1797 May 28 (Box 3, Item 405)
  Regarding payment on mortgage due in Dutchess County.
- Rochefontaine, Lieutenant Colonel Stephen. Order for General Court Martial. West Point, NY, 1797 September 19 (Box 1, Item 9)
- Houdin, Captain. Letter to Henry Glen. Albany, 1797 November 1 (Box 5, Item 580)
  Regarding army clothing.
- Plymouth Commonwealth of Massachusetts. Company Military Orders, 1799 July 4-1800 April 12 (Box 4, Item 522)
  Diary book of orders given.
- Hopkins, Reuben, clerk of Orange County. Bond for Peter Lamouraux and Oliver Gridley, 1800 September 24 (Box 3, Item 412)
- Williams, General John. Letter to General Fish. Salem, 1801 February 20 (Box 3, Item 396)
  Letter states that he is enclosing $100.
- Clinton, George, Governor of New York. Commission to William Hudson, 1802 March 4 (Box 4, Item 503)
  Rank of cornet.
- Clinton, George, Governor of New York. Appointment of Samuel S. Seward (Oversize), 1803 March 23 (Box OS-Small, Item 528)
- Laurence, John. Letter to George Simpson, Cashier of Bank of United States. New York, 1803 December 6 (Box 3, Item 395)
  Regarding 60 dollars to credit.
- Burnet, Robert R. of Orange County. Letter. Albany, 1804 February 15 (Box 2, Item 210)
  Regarding election of governor after Governor Clinton.
- Clinton, George, Governor of New York. Commission to William Hudson, 1804 March 31 (Box 4, Item 502)
  Rank of Second Lieutenant.
- Cadwell, Richard. Account of Samuel Moffatt, 1805 June 27 (Box 6, Item 628)
- Gelston, Maltby. Certificate of 124 gallons of brandy imported on the Centurion, 1805 September 24 (Box 3, Item 398)
- Clark, Thomas and Richard Lumax and Jane Garrison. Deed, 1806 May 20 (Box 2, Item 238)
- Clinton, George. Letter to Governor Tompkins. Washington City, 1808 January 21 (Box 1, Item 60)
  Regarding defenses in New York City against hostile ships.
- Smith, Israel. Letter to Jonathan Williams, Sup't USMA. Rutland, 1808 January 27 (Box 1, Item 38)
- Burnet, Samuel. Deed with James Davis. New Windsor, 1808 April 21 (Box 3, Item 463)
- Burnet, Henry. Deed with James Davis. Orange County, 1809 March 9 (Box 3, Item 458)
- Davis, James. Articles of Agreement with Henry Burnet. New Windsor, 1809 March 17 (Box 3, Item 466)
- Clark, General Alured and General Fleurs (?) and General Burrand. Assignment of Off Reckonings. Great George Street, 1810 June 27 (Box 1, Item 49)
- Burnet, Samuel. Mortgage with James Davis. New Windsor, 1811 January 21 (Box 3, Item 464)
- Eagle Glass Works. $3 order by Jason Smith. Port Elizabeth, NJ, 1811 May 8 (Box 3, Item 453)
- Hudson, William. Obligation for $1751.56 to George Thompson, 1811 September 16 (Box 1, Item 145)
- Hudson, William. Deed to George Thompson, 1811 September 16 (Box 1, Item 153)
- Eagle Glass Works. $10.43 order by Jason Smith. Port Elizabeth, NJ, 1812 January 24 (Box 3, Item 452)
- Eagle Glass Works. $2.75 order by Jason Smith. Port Elizabeth, NJ, 1812 July 6 (Box 3, Item 454)
- Eagle Glass Works. Order for Lamp Oil. Port Elizabeth, NJ, 1812 July 10 (Box 3, Item 455)
- Vermont Glass Factory note. $1, Samuel Swift, President. Pay to J. Chever, 1813 July 6 (Box 1, Item 67)
- Vermont Glass Factory note. $1.75. Samuel Swift, President. Pay to L. Rugg, 1813 August 4 (Box 1, Item 78)
- Vermont Glass Factory note. $1.25. Samuel Swift, President. Pay to W.P. Hooker, 1813 August 17 (Box 1, Item 80)
- Vermont Glass Factory note. $1. Samuel Swift, President. Pay to J. Clark, 1813 September 14 (Box 1, Item 68)
- Hudson, Jonathan. Obligation to William Horton, 1813 November 8 (Box 1, Item 149)
- Hudson, William and Susannah, wife. Conveyance to J. Hudson, 1813 November 8 (Box 1, Item 152)
- Vermont Glass Factory note. $1. Samuel Swift, President, 1813 December 1 (Box 1, Item 84)
- Vermont Glass Factory note. $1. Samuel Swift, President, 1813 December 1 (Box 1, Item 86)
- Hudson, Jonathan. Mortgage with George Thompson, 1813 December 15 (Box 1, Item 147)
- Vermont Glass Factory note. $1 Samuel Swift, President. Pay to C. Suy, 1813 (Box 1, Item 91)
- Vermont Glass Factory note. $1. Samuel Swift, President. Pay to W. Worth, 1814 January 1 (Box 1, Item 69)
- Vermont Glass Factory note. $1. Samuel Swift, President. Pay to W. Wales, 1814 January 1 (Box 1, Item 72)
- Vermont Glass Factory note. $1. Samuel Swift, President. Pay to W. Wales, 1814 January 1 (Box 1, Item 73)
- Vermont Glass Factory note. $1. Samuel Swift, President. Pay to W. Wales, 1814 January 1 (Box 1, Item 74)
- Vermont Glass Factory note. $1.50. Samuel Swift, President. Pay to H. King, 1814 January 1 (Box 1, Item 77)
- Vermont Glass Factory note. $1. Samuel Swift, President. Pay to W. Wales, 1814 January 1 (Box 1, Item 85)
- Vermont Glass Factory note. $1. Samuel Swift, President. Pay to W. Wales, 1814 January 1 (Box 1, Item 88)
- Vermont Glass Factory note. $1.50. Samuel Swift, President. Pay to W. Wales, 1814 January 1 (Box 1, Item 89)
- Vermont Glass Factory note. $3. Samuel Swift, President. Pay to J. Smith, 1814 January 10 (Box 1, Item 71)
- Vermont Glass Factory note. $3. Samuel Swift, President. Pay to H. Allen, 1814 January 10 (Box 1, Item 76)
- Vermont Glass Factory note. $1. Samuel Swift, President. Pay to B. Swift, 1814 January 10 (Box 1, Item 87)
- Vermont Glass Factory note. $1. Samuel Swift, President. Pay to W. Sebor, 1814 June 1 (Box 1, Item 70)
- Vermont Glass Factory note. $1. Samuel Swift, President. Pay to H. King, 1814 June 1 (Box 1, Item 75)
- Vermont Glass Factory note. $1.75. Samuel Swift, President, 1814 June 1 (Box 1, Item 81)
- Columbia County Justice Court. Court records, 1814 June 22-1815 March 31 (Box 5, Item 601)
  Ledger includes liquor records from 1827-1829.
- Vermont Glass Factory note. $2. Samuel Swift, President, 1814 (Box 1, Item 66)
- Lamoreux, Peter. Deed with Susannah Davenport. Town of Monroe, Orange County, NY, 1817 March 15 (Box 4, Item 486)
- Mearns, Alexander. Deed with Bartley F. Tuthill. Cornwall, Orange County, NY, 1818 May 29 (Box 6, Item 631)
- Webber, Ignatius. Gloucester State and County tax form, 1818 (Box 3, Item 399)
- Baker, Thomas. Account of taxes paid by Samuel Coffin. Concord, 1819 September 4 (Box 3, Item 400)
- Evans, James. Letter to Smith Thompson, Secretary of Navy. Washington, DC, 1820 January 29 (Box 5, Item 584)
  Regarding appointment of Samuel Anderson.
- Wright, David and Daniel Wright, his son. Articles of Agreement. New Windsor, 1821 December 17 (Box 3, Item 320)
- Jackson, Andrew. Letter to Major Sylvanus Thayer. Nashville, 1821 March 13 (Box 2, Item 282)
  Regarding nephew's appointment to the Military Academy at West Point. Contains presidential signature.
- Worth, W.J. Letter to Sylvanus Thayer, Sup't of West Point. West Point, 1822 August 10 (Box 3, Item 420)
  Requisition for Army requirements for use of Corps of Cadets.
- Worth, William J. Letter to Mr. Robinson, Cashier, U.S. Branch Bank, NY. West Point, 1822 July 8 (Box 1, Item 109)
- Townsend, David. Letter to William Young, merchant. West Chester, PA, 1822 November 12 (Box 2, Item 299)
- Meigs, Colonel Return Jonathan. Obituary, 1823 January 28 (Box 6, Item 618)
- Van Buren, Martin. Letter to Major Worth. New York, 1823 May 30 (Box 5, Item 569)
  Introduction of son. Contains presidential signature.
- Halsey, Apolar. Sale of pew in Blooming Grove Church, 1823 November 6 (Box 1, Item 144)
- Naval Captains. Letter approving uniforms. Washington, DC, 1825 August 24 (Box 5, Item 583)
- Brown, Archibald. Deed with Benjamin Brown. New Windsor, 1826 February 7 (Box 3, Item 465)
- Roe, Joseph v. Moses Decker. Action of the Court signed by Edward L. Welling, 1827 August 20 (Box 2, Item 228)
  Orders to pay 3 dollars.
- Hudson, William. Indenture to Jonathan Hudson, 1827 May 16 (Box 1, Item 148)
- Thayer, Sylvanus. Letter to Colonel George Gibson. Military Academy, West Point, NY, 1827 September 15 (Box 3, Item 436)
  Regarding application of Lieutenant Whelock.
- Niles, N. Statement of Account with US Military Academy. West Point, NY, 1828 April 8-28 (Box 4, Item 500)
- Worth, W. Letter to Hon. S.L. Lorthard. U.S. Military Academy, West Point, 1828 May 10 (Box 1, Item 115)
- Thusuen, S. Receipt of Joseph Roe. New York, 1828 August 25 (Box 6, Item 632)
- Niles, N. Account of Colonel Sylvanus Thayer. Paris, 1828 November-1829 February (Box 3, Item 431)
- Roe, Joseph. Permit to retail certain items at store. Warwick, 1828 (Box 2, Item 227)
- Armisted, Gen. Walker Keith. Letter to Gen. Alexander Macomb. Boston, MA, 1829 November 23 (Box 1, Item 2)
- Roe, Joseph. Assorted receipts. Newburgh, 1820s (Box 1, Item 160)
  15 receipts.
- Roe, Joseph. Assorted receipts. Newburgh, 1820s (Box 1, Item 161)
- Roe, Joseph. Assorted receipts. Newburgh, 1820s (Box 1, Item 162)
- Roe, Joseph. Assorted receipts. Newburgh, 1820s (Box 1, Item 163)
- Roe, Joseph. Assorted receipts. Newburgh, 1820s (Box 1, Item 164)
- Roe, Joseph. Assorted receipts. Newburgh, 1820s (Box 1, Item 165)
- Roe, Joseph. Assorted receipts. Newburgh, 1820s (Box 1, Item 166)
- Roe, Joseph. Receipts from Crawford & Co. Newburgh, 1820s (Box 1, Item 167)
  12 receipts.
- Roe, Joseph. Receipts from Law, Bevridge & Co.; A&M. H. Belknap; R.C.S. Hendrie., 1820s (Box 1, Item 168)
  11 receipts.
- Roe, Joseph. Assorted receipts, 1820s (Box 1, Item 169)
- Roe, Joseph. Assorted receipts, 1820s (Box 2, Item 170)
- Roe, Joseph. Assorted receipts, 1820s (Box 2, Item 171)
- NY Senate. Report on petition of David Godwin, 1831 March 12 (Box 4, Item 514)
  Stating that he is entitled to his bounty.
- VanTasell, Albert. Deed to Reuben Rose. Cornwall, Orange County, NY, 1831 April 7 (Box 2, Item 281)
- Coleman, Abner, Jr. Deed, 1831 May 16 (Box 1, Item 155)
- Mottre (?) G.L. Letter to Gen. J.G. Swift. Newport, 1831 August 8 (Box 1, Item 96)
  Regarding cutter-plough diagram.
- NY Senate. Report on petition of Jacob Shew, 1833 February 9 (Box 4, Item 512)
  Report states that Shew is entitled to his bounty.
- Account book. Philipstown, Putnam County, NY, 1833-1836 (Box 4, Item 525)
  Original returned, copy only. 120 pages on microfilm.
- LaFayette, French General. Silk Ribbons engraved by Tiller and J. Yeager. Philadelphia, 1834 (Box 5, Item 597)
- Ringgold, Major Samuel. Memorandum that articles of clothing are inspected. Fort Monroe, 1834 April 21 (Box 2, Item 191)
- Clinton, C.A. Letter to Major William Popham of West Chester County. New York, 1834 June 30 (Box 2, Item 208)
  Letter is to correct the record regarding loss of Fort Clinton during Revolutionary War.
- Goodale, W. Bank note of Bank of Newburgh. For Alexander Piper, 1834 August 20 (Box 1, Item 159)
- Weir, Robert W. Letter to Colonel G.P. Morris, editor of The New-York Mirror. West Point, 1834 December 19 (Box 1, Item 131)
  Letter states that he sold a picture to Mr. Stuyvesant.
- Thayer, Sylvanus. Letter to Colonel W.J. Worth. Boston, 1835 February 8 (Box 1, Item 107)
  Regarding conditions at Fort Independence and Fort Warren.
- NY Senate. Report on petition of Uriah Jacobs, 1835 February 24 (Box 4, Item 513)
  Regarding compensation for Revolutionary War service.
- Ripley, Captain James W. Letter to S. Lansing, Jr. West Point, 1836 June 26 (Box 3, Item 325)
  States that application is enclosed.
- Adams, W.H. Letter to General J.G. Swift. Lyons, 1836 December 6 (Box 1, Item 95)
- L'Hommedieu, B. Day book, 1836-1869 (Volume Clark 1, Item 557)
- Bratt, John. Letter to Joel R. Poinsett, Secretary of War. Old Point Comfort, VA, 1837 August 17 (Box 5, Item 608)
  Regarding return to the military academy.
- Burgnan, O.H. Letter to "Dear Griff." Norfolk, VA, 1837 November 20 (Box 3, Item 394)
- Lain, Jonathan. Letter to any regular Baptist Church. Orange County, NY, 1838 June 9 (Box 2, Item 232)
  Regarding Sister Polly's Request for Disunion; she is a member in Good Standing.
- Lain, Jonathan. Letter to the Baptist Church at Warwick, Orange County, NY, 1838 December 22 (Box 2, Item 231)
  Regarding bad conduct of Mrs. Lain at the Baptist Church of Orange County--laughing and sneezing.
- Sly, Arthur B. Account Book. Orange County, 1838-1843 (Box 2, Item 181)
- Poinsett, Joel R. Letter to John Bratt, Esq. of Troy. War Department, 1839 January 7 (Box 5, Item 607)
  Regarding appointment in army.
- Holt, Jacob H., agent of purveyor. Duplicate of payroll of persons employed at cadets' mess hall. West Point, NY, 1839 January-February (Box 4, Item 518)
- Holt, Jacob H., agent of purveyor. Duplicate of payroll of persons employed at cadets' mess hall. West Point, NY, 1839 January-February (Box 4, Item 520)
- Holt, Jacob H., agent of purveyor. Duplicate of payroll of persons employed at cadets' mess hall. West Point, NY, 1839 March-April (Box 4, Item 515)
- Holt, Jacob H., agent of purveyor. Duplicate of payroll of persons employed at cadets' mess hall. West Point, NY, 1839 March-April (Box 4, Item 519)
- Holt, Jacob H., agent of purveyor. Duplicate of payroll of persons employed at cadets' mess hall. West Point, NY, May 1839 (Box 4, Item 517)
- Holt, Jacob H., agent of purveyor. Duplicate of payroll of persons employed at cadets' mess hall. West Point, NY, 1839 May (Box 4, Item 521)
- Leggett, Abraham, President of the Society of Cincinnati. Printed draft to Anthony Lamb to pay $21.68, 1839 May 18 (Box 1, Item 36)
- Hamilton, C.S. Letter to G.S. Hamilton. West Point, 1839 August 30 (Box 1, Item 57)
- Bull, Alanson. Deed to Reuben Rose. Cornwall, Orange County, NY, 1840 March 3 (Box 2, Item 280)